dmdsolutions.co.in 2018-12-19

# DMD Solutions-About Us |IT Company |Software Development Services |Smart Work |Easily Customized | Software solutions | dmd solutions | dmd|

## Commitment

DMD Solutions intends to protect the privacy of its users on its website being and the privacy of their data provided to DMD Solutions from time to time. The privacy of our Website users is important to us and we are strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal and other information secure. We encourage you to read our privacy statement to understand what types of personally identifiable information ,we collect and how we use this information. Our Website collects preliminary personal information that allows us to identify you as a user and know more about your requirements. Information (if any) provided by you on such web domains may be dealt by them in the manner provided by the privacy statements of such third party web domains. This Privacy Policy only deals with your information shared with us and we shall in no manner be liable/bound for protection of information (if any), which may be shared by you on such third party web domains. We encourage you to very carefully review the privacy policy of any third-party website you visit before using it and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information on such websites. 

## How does DMD Solutions protect my Personal Information?

DMD Solutions is committed to protecting the privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. Whenever DMD Solutions obtains personal information from you, our Website uses commercially reasonable efforts and general industry standards to protect it from any unauthorized access or disclosure. Save as otherwise provided herein, access to your personal information is limited to DMD Solutions’s personnel and such authorized third parties who may host your data on our behalf or may assist us in providing the products and services requested by you. DMD Solutions uses its best endeavours to maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that aim to protect your information against loss, misuse, damage, modification, and unauthorized access or disclosure. However, DMD Solutions assumes no liability whatever for any disclosure of personal information due to unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or any other acts or omissions beyond reasonable control of DMD Solutions. 

## Your Consent

This document is published by virtue of a legal requirement under the provisions of the Information Technology Act, 2000 that requires ‘intermediaries’ to publish the rules and regulations, privacy policy and terms for access or usage of the website and is primarily governed by Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries guidelines) Rules, 2011 and Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011. 

## How does DMD Solutions use the information that it collects?

Your information may be used by us and/or authorized third parties/service partners to support your interaction with us and to provide you our Services and products that we offer. By submitting your personal information to DMD Solutions, you expressly acknowledge and consent to DMD Solutions to use such information and to process the same in a manner deemed fit by DMD Solutions. This may involve conducting data analysis, research based on reviews about deals, transfer of your information to third party experts for the purpose of outsourcing services offered to you by DMD Solutions etc. 

## Will DMD Solutions change privacy policy in the future?

Your information may be used by us and/or authorized third parties/service partners to support your interaction with us and to provide you our Services and products that we offer. By submitting your personal information to DMD Solutions, you expressly acknowledge and consent to DMD Solutions to use such information and to process the same in a manner deemed fit by DMD Solutions. This may involve conducting data analysis, research based on reviews about deals, transfer of your information to third party experts for the purpose of outsourcing services offered to you by DMD Solutions etc.
